CONTACT



+374 33 958 957



vahnell13@gmail.com



in Linkedin



GitHub

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 YEREVAN STATE COLLEGE **OF INFORMATICS**

• Technician-Mechatronic

2023 - 2024 **PICSART ACADEMY**

• Computer Science and JavaScript Renaissance **Program**

SKILLS

- JavaScript / Core JS
- HTML/CSS
- OOP
- DOM
- React JS
- Redux, Redux Toolkit
- TypeScript
- REST API, Axios
- Vite
- Linux
- Computer Architecture
- Git/GitHub
- Basecamp
- Tailwind CSS
- Material UI

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Russian Intermediate
- Armenian Native

VAHAN KOCHKANYAN

FrontEnd Developer

PROFILE

I am a FrontEnd developer with experience in JavaScript and various related technologies. I specialize in React.js, TypeScript, and Redux and I also have knowledge in programming fundamentals such as OOP, DOM, and working with APIs. I completed training at Picsart Academy in the JavaScript Renaissance group as a FrontEnd Developer, where I learned to build modern, reliable, and user-friendly interfaces with my team.

Additionally, my previous experience includes service in the Armed Forces, where I developed teamwork skills and remained resilient in challenging situations.

EXPERIENCE

CODE REPUBLIC LAB, PICSART ACADEMY NOV 2023 - JAN 2024

As a JavaScript Lab student, my main focus is on mastering JavaScript by engaging in hands-on exercises and interactive sessions. I actively participated in hands-on activities to deepen my understanding of JavaScript concepts, improve problem-solving skills, and gain valuable real-world programming experience.

FRONTEND INTERN DEVELOPER MOVIATO, PICSART ACADEMY JAN 2024 - APRIL 2024

I have worked on the MOVIATO project, where I applied my skills in JavaScript, React.js, Redux, and other web development technologies. Within the scope of this project, I developed user-friendly and functional interface while ensuring the system's efficiency. This experience also allowed me to refine my coding practices and effectively collaborate in a team environment.

SALES MANAGER, FNET TELECOM JUN 2024 - SEP 2024

- Successfully managed the sales process by effectively presenting the company's services.
- Possess strong communication skills, enabling the establishment of long-term relationships with clients.

ABOUT ME

Armed Forces of Armenia, Soldier (2021-2023), participated in the September 13th war.